1stfreehosting.com 2012-01-08

# 

* * *

Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Findhosting.org collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of the Findhosting.org Web Site (each, a “User”).

Privacy  
Findhosting.org is committed to safeguarding the information Users entrust to Findhosting.org and believes every User should know how Findhosting.org utilizes the information collected from the Web Site.  
This Web Site is not directed at children under 13 years of age.

The Information We Collect  
Findhosting.org may collect personally identifiable information from Users in a variety of ways, including through online forms for ordering products and services, and other instances where Users are invited to volunteer such information.  
Findhosting.org may also collect information about how Users use our Web Site, for example, by tracking the number of unique views received by the pages of the Web Site, or the domains from which Users originate.  
We may use “cookies” to track how Users use our Web Site.  
A cookie is a piece of software that a Web server can store on the Users’ PC and use to identify the User should they visit the web site again.  
While not all of the information that we collect from Users is personally identifiable, it may be associated with personally identifiable information that Users provide us through our Web Site.  
We currently use third party ad software to serve ads on our site.  
The cookies received with banner ads served by this software is used to collect and build anonymous behavioral profiles by these companies to deliver targeted ads and tracking referrals.

How We Use Information  
Findhosting.org may use personally identifiable information collected through our Web Site to contact Users regarding products and services offered by Findhosting.org and its trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners, and otherwise to enhance Users’ experience with Findhosting.org and such affiliates, independent contractors and business partners.  
Findhosting.org may also use information collected through our Web Site for research regarding the effectiveness of the Web Site and the marketing, advertising and sales efforts of Findhosting.org, its trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners.

Disclosure of Information  
Findhosting.org may disclose information collected from Users to trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners who will use the information for the purposes outlined above.  
We may also disclose aggregate, anonymous data based on information collected from Users to investors and potential partners.  
Finally, we may transfer information collected from Users in connection with a sale of Findhosting.org’ business.

Maintenance of Information  
Information about Users that is maintained on our systems is protected using industry standard security measures.  
However, we cannot guarantee that the information submitted to, maintained on, or transmitted from our systems will be completely secure.

Questions  
Users may direct questions concerning this Privacy Policy by email to privacy@Findhosting.
